

РезюмеSenior JavaScript Developer

Personal Data

2

Serhii Pimenov



serhii@pimenov.com.ua



+380635022967



Ukraine, Kyiv



nimenov com ца



aithuh com/olton

Skills

TypeScript

Html

CSS/LESS

SQL

PHP

Rust

Languages

Ukrainian •••••
English ••••

Profile

I am an experienced JavaScript Developer. I have over 25 years of experience as a programmer and over 10 of those have been professional web development.

Currently, I specialize in creating web components using HTML, JavaScript and CSS, as well as sites using Astro and Metro UI, and I work as a Frontend Lead at Korzh.com, where I improve my skills in JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML and CSS/LESS. I have in-depth knowledge of modern front-end technologies and strive to apply them to create innovative solutions. I am looking for an opportunity to develop in a team of professionals and contribute to the company's success.

Education

лип 1993 - лип 1997

Tavri Institute of Entrepreneurship and Law

Simferopol

Bachelor of Laws

Employment

січ 2022 - Нинішній

Frontend Lead in Korzh.com

Korzh.com, Kyiv

Development of the company website, development of EasyQuery.JS, EasyData.JS, Easy.Report components, development of demo applications

січ 2021 - січ 2022

Freelance Web Developer

Kyiv

Metro UI library development, custom site development, consulting on site development and maintenance

лип 2013 - січ 2021

Director of Department for perspective development

Internet Invest, Kyiv

Development of the DNmarket.com domain supermarket, study of the possibilities of introducing the latest technologies into the company's processes.

січ 2006 - лип 2013

Freelance Web Developer

Kyiv

Development of custom sites, development of the 1st version of the library of Metro UI components

Personal qualities

Punctual, motivated, honest, reliable, flexible, executive

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position I am applying for.